const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "A human-powered vehicle with two wheels.",
    answer: "bicycle",
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is a common pet with whiskers and a tail?",
    answer: "cat",
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    question: "This country is known for its kangaroos and koalas.",
    answer: "Australia",
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "It's a tropical fruit with a tough outer layer and sweet inner flesh.",
    answer: "pineapple",
  },

  {
    id: 5,
    question: "The smallest unit of an element.",
    answer: "atom",
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    question: "An ancient wonder in Egypt with a triangular shape.",
    answer: "pyramids",
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "This Italian dish consists of thin layers of pasta, sauce, and cheese.",
    answer: "lasagna",
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    question: "A popular mobile operating system developed by Google.",
    answer: "Android",
  },

  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "This instrument is known for its black and white keys and is commonly found in classical music.",
    answer: "Piano",
  },

  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "This iconic British rock band was formed in 1960 and is known for hits like 'Bohemian Rhapsody'.",
    answer: "Queen",
  },

  {
    id: 11,
    question: "The fourth planet from the sun in our solar system.",
    answer: "Mars",
  },

  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "A legendary creature with a single, spiraled horn on its forehead.",
    answer: "Unicorn",
  },

  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "A Southeast Asian country known for its beautiful beaches and temples.",
    answer: "Thailand",
  },

  {
    id: 14,
    question:
      "A sport where players hit a small, lightweight ball back and forth over a net with a racket.",
    answer: "Tennis",
  },
];

export default questions;
